(CLASSIC ROCK MUSIC)
♪ STACY'S MOM HAS
GOT IT GOIN' ON ♪
♪ STACY, CAN I COME
OVER AFTER SCHOOL ♪
♪ AFTER SCHOOL ♪
♪ WE CAN HANG
AROUND BY THE POOL ♪
♪ HANG BY THE POOL ♪
♪ DID YOUR MOM GET BACK
FROM HER BUSINESS TRIP ♪
♪ BUSINESS TRIP ♪
♪ IS SHE THERE, OR IS SHE
TRYING TO GIVE ME THE SLIP ♪
♪ GIVE ME THE SLIP ♪
♪ YOU KNOW, I'M NOT THE
LITTLE BOY THAT I USED TO BE ♪
♪ I'M ALL GROWN UP NOW ♪
♪ BABY, CAN'T YOU SEE ♪
♪ STACY'S MOM HAS
GOT IT GOIN' ON ♪
♪ SHE'S ALL I WANT ♪
♪ AND I'VE WAITED FOR SO LONG ♪
♪ STACY, CAN'T YOU SEE ♪
♪ YOU'RE JUST NOT
THE GIRL FOR ME ♪
♪ I KNOW IT MIGHT BE WRONG BUT ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE WITH STACY'S MOM ♪
♪ STACY'S MOM HAS
GOT IT GOIN' ON ♪
♪ STACY, DO YOU REMEMBER
WHEN I MOWED YOUR LAWN ♪
♪ MOWED YOUR LAWN ♪
♪ YOUR MOM CAME OUT
WITH JUST A TOWEL ON ♪
♪ TOWEL ON ♪
♪ I COULD TELL SHE LIKED ME
FROM THE WAY SHE STARED ♪
♪ THE WAY SHE STARED ♪
♪ AND THE WAY SHE SAID ♪
♪ YOU MISSED A SPOT OVER THERE ♪
♪ A SPOT OVER THERE ♪
♪ AND I KNOW THAT YOU
THINK IT'S JUST A FANTASY ♪
♪ BUT SINCE YOUR
DAD WALKED OUT ♪
♪ YOUR MOM COULD
USE A GUY LIKE ME ♪
♪ STACY'S MOM HAS
GOT IT GOIN' ON ♪
♪ SHE'S ALL I WANT ♪
♪ AND I'VE WAITED FOR SO LONG ♪
♪ STACY, CAN'T YOU SEE ♪
♪ YOU'RE JUST NOT
THE GIRL FOR ME ♪
♪ I KNOW IT MIGHT BE WRONG BUT ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE WITH STACY'S MOM ♪
♪ STACY'S MOM HAS
GOT IT GOIN' ON ♪
♪ SHE'S GOT IT GOING ON ♪
♪ SHE'S ALL I WANT AND
I'VE WAITED FOR SO LONG ♪
♪ WAITED AND WAITED ♪
♪ STACY, CAN'T YOU SEE ♪
♪ YOU'RE JUST NOT
THE GIRL FOR ME ♪
♪ I KNOW IT MIGHT BE WRONG ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE WITH ♪
♪ STACY'S MOM, OH, OH ♪
♪ WAIT A MINUTE ♪
♪ STACY, CAN'T YOU SEE ♪
♪ YOU'RE JUST NOT
THE GIRL FOR ME ♪
♪ I KNOW IT MIGHT BE WRONG BUT ♪
♪ I'M IN LOVE WITH STACY'S MOM ♪